Guide to the Cornell University student and faculty cabinet photographs,1892.
Cornell University student and faculty cabinet photographs,1892
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University student and faculty cabinet photographs, 1892.
6692
Henry, Hicks
25 items.
Photographs
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cabinet photographs of Cornell University faculty and students from 1892.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Cornell University class of 1892.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Cabinet photographs of Cornell University faculty and students from 1892.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Hicks, Henry,; Cornell University--Students.; Cornell University--Faculty.; Cornell University--Alumni and alumnae.; Cornell University.Class of 1892.
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.; Cabinet photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Professors
  - Liberty Hyde Bailey, First Dean, College of Agriculture, 1892 (Box 1)
  - Issac Phillips Roberts, Professor of Agriculture, First Director, College of Agriculture, 1892 (Box 1)
  - Issac Phillips Roberts, Professor of Agriculture, First Director, College of Agriculture, 1892 (Box 1)
  - William Russell Dudley, Professor of Botany, 1892 (Box 1)
  - Albert Nelson Prentiss, Professor of Botany, 1892 (Box 1)
  - Simon Henry Gage, Head of Department of Histology & Embryology, 1892 (Box 1)
  - Professor Rowlee (?), Professor of Botany, 1892 (Box 1)
  - Professor Munson (?), 1892 (Box 1)
  - James Edward Oliver, Professor of Mathematics, Head of Department of Mathematics, 1892 (Box 1)
  - James Law, Professor of Veterinary Medicine & Surgery, First Director of NYS Veterinary College, 1892 (Box 1)
- Students
  - Edwin C. Powell, 1892 (Box 1)
  - E. A. de Louza, 1892 (Box 1)
  - Herbert F. Burrage, 1892 (Box 1)
  - Beulah Taylor, 1892 (Box 1)
  - W. A. Baldwin, 1892 (Box 1)
  - Mary E. Martin / Mrs. G. Ashley, 1892 (Box 1)
  - Harry D. Howe, 1892 (Box 1)
  - Arthur S. Eakle, 1892 (Box 1)
  - F. W. Card, 1892 (Box 1)
  - Charles H. Royce, 1892 (Box 1)
  - E. A. de Sobra Souza, 1892 (Box 1)
  - C. A. Duniway, 1892 (Box 1)
  - Atoji Tanahashi, 1892 (Box 1)
  - Charles Moore, 1892 (Box 1)
  - Benjamin Ide Wheeler, 1892 (Box 1)